A Guide to the City College of New York collection of the Russell Sage Foundation Library FA1208
Rockefeller Archive Center
- American Friends Service Committee, 1942 Annual Report, 1943 (Box 21)
- Jones, Rufus M., A Great Experiment, 1942 (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, The Japanese Evacuation: A Message from the American Friends Serves Committee to the Society of Friends and to our Fellow Christians, 1942 (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, Looking Toward the Post-War World - Statement of the Friends Conference on Peace an Reconstruction held at Wilmington, Ohio, 1942 August 31-September 4 (Box 21)
- The Salvation Army National Research Bureau, Pilgrim's Progress: 20th Century. The Story of Salvation Army Officership, 1950 (Box 21)
- Salvation Army Press, A Review of the Salvation Army Land Colony in California, 1903 (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, Some Quaker Approaches to the Race Problem, 1946 (Box 21)
- New Zealand Council for Educational Research, An Experiment in Self-Government, 1938 (Box 21)
- State of New York, Annual Report of the Commissioners of Emigration for the Year Ending 1978 December 31, 1847-1860 (Box 22)
- New York, Emigration of the State of New York: from the Organization of the Commission, 1847 May 5, to 1860, Inclusive, Together with Tables and Reports, and Other Official Documents, 1863-1868 (Box 22)
- New York, Annual Report of the Commissioners of Emigration for the Year Ending 1884 December 31, 1869-1877 (Box 22)
- New York, Annual Report of the Commissioners of Emigration of the State of New York, 1863 December 31 (Box 22)
- New York, Annual Report of the Commissioners of Emigration of the State of New York, 1869 December 31 (Box 22)
- Associated Jewish Charities of Chicago, Report of the Jewish Charities of Chicago, Vol. 13, 1913 (Box 22)
- University of Pennsylvania, Twentieth Report of the Henry Phipps Institute for the Study, Treatment and Prevention of Tuberculosis, 1928 (Box 22)
- Cambridge University, Infant Mortality, 1928 (Box 22)
- State of Michigan Department of Labor, Labor Laws, 1949 (Box 22)
- Industrial Commission of Minnesota, Labor Laws, 1929 (Box 22)
- Federated Jewish Charities, Baltimore Federated Jewish Charities Annual Reports, 1907-1915 (Box 22A)
- Massachusetts. Bureau of Immigration, Second Annual Report of the Bureau of Immigration, 1920 (Box 22A)
- Massachusetts, Bureau of Immigration - Who is your neighbor, 1918 (Box 22A)
- Massachusetts, Bureau of Immigration, Americanization for Club Women (Box 22A)
- Massachusetts, Bureau of Immigration, Immigrant Races in Massachusetts - The Greeks, 1919 (Box 22A)
- Massachusetts, Department of Education, Annual Reports of the Division of Immigration and Americanization, 1920-1940 (Box 22A)
- Washington, D.C.: U.S. G.P.O, Memorandum to America, the DP Story: The Final Report, 1952 (Box 23)
- United States, Displaced Persons Commission, The Displaced Persons Commission: Six Months of Operation, 1948 July 1-December 31, 1949 (Box 23)
- United States, The Displaced Persons Commission: The Displaced Persons Commission: Third Semiannual report to the President and the Congress, 1950 February 1 (Box 23)
- United States Department of Justice, United States Immigration Laws, General Information (Box 23)
- United States Department of Justice, USA "Citizenship" Naturalization Requirements and Procedure (Box 23)
- United States Department of Justice, Alien Address Report Program, 1953 (Box 23)
- United States.; Immigration and Naturalization Service, Road to USA Citizenship, Collection of Helpful Facts and Necessary Information for Alien Seeking Citizenship, 1952 (Box 23)
- United States.; Immigration and Naturalization Service, Our Constitution and Government, Lessons on the Constitution and Government of the United States for the use in the Public Schools by Candidates for Citizenship, 1941 (Box 23)
- Annual Report of the Commissioners of Emigration, of the State of New York, 1861 December 31 (Box 23)
- Immigration and Naturalization Service, Annual Report of the Immigration and Naturalization Service for the year ended 1943 June 30 (Box 23)
- International Labour Office, International Labour Office, Legislative Series (Volumes 1-3), 1933 (Box 23)
- Illinois Department of Registration and Education, The Educational Needs of Immigrants in Illinois, 1920 (Box 23)
- Illinois Immigrants Commission, The Immigrant and Coal Mining Communities of Illinois, 1920 (Box 23)
- Hawaii Board of Immigration, 1907 (Box 23)
- International Labour Office, General Subject Catalogue 1919-1934, 1935 (Box 23)
- International Labour Office, General Subject Index 1935-1941, 1942 (Box 23)
- International Labour Office, Legislative Series, Complete List of Laws and Regulations Published in the Legislative Series from 1920-1926, 1927 (Box 23)
- Board of Immigration, Labor and Statistics, Reports of the Board of Immigration, Labor and Statistics to the Governor of the Territory of Hawaii, 1912-1915 (Box 23)
- Department of Citizenship and Immigration, Citizen, Volume 5, No. 4, 1958 (Box 23)
- Department of Citizenship and Immigration, Annual Reports, Department of Citizenship and Immigration, 1951-1955 (Box 23)
- Department of Mines and Resources, Report of Immigration Branch Including Report of Soldier Settlement of Canada, 1937-1939, 1946-1948 (Box 23)
- International Labour Office, Legislative Series, Supplement Recent Labour Legislation, 1937 (Box 23)
- The Rockefeller Foundation, Annual Report, 1914 (Box 23)
- National Information Bureau, Wise Giving (Box 23)
- National Information Bureau, On Guard to Protect Gifts and Givers (Box 23)
- Ellison, Jerome, Who Gets Your Charity Dollars (Box 23)
- National Information Bureau, From Orangeburg to Okolona, 1921-1922 (Box 23)
- National Information Bureau, National Information Bureau Report, 1919-1920 (Box 23)
- National Information Bureau, Keep Faith with the Contributor, 1949 (Box 23)
- National Information Bureau, Keep Faith with the Contributor, 1947 (Box 23)
- National Information Bureau, The Bureau Reports to You, 1943 (Box 23)
- National Information Bureau, National Information Bureau Report, 1918-1919 (Box 23)
- National Information Bureau Help Safeguard Philanthropy, 1955 (Box 23)
- National Information Bureau, Safeguard We Must the Contributor's Trust, 1957-1966 (23a)
- National Information Bureau, Keep Philanthropy True, 1945 (23a)
- National Information Bureau, Wise Giving Helps Philanthropy True, 1953 (23a)
- National Information Bureau, Help Keep Philanthropy True, 1953 (23a)
- National Information Bureau, Help Keep Philanthropy True, 1954 (23a)
- National Information Bureau, Help Keep Philanthropy True, 1956 (23a)
- National Information Bureau, Help Keep Philanthropy True, 1963 (23a)
- National Information Bureau, Help Keep Philanthropy True, 1971 (23a)
- Pan American Union Division of Agriculture and Conservation, The Role of Conservation in the Education Program of Latin America, 1951 (23a)
- Charities and Publication Committee, Field Department Bulletin, 1907-1908 (23a)
- Charities and Publication Committee, Field Department Bulletin, 2008-2009 (23a)
- Post War World Council, Let's Keep the Tolls of Plenty: Big Business Must Not Get Government War Plants, 1944 (23a)
- Post War World Council, Democracy and Japanese Americans, 1942 (23a)
- Post War World Council, The Coming Generation in Europe, 1943 (23a)
- Post War World Council, Conscription, The Test of the Peace, 1944 (23a)
- Post War World Council, You Can Win the Peace Now, 1943 (23a)
- Post War World Council, International Cartels and World Peace, a Condensation of a Study Prepared for an Published by the Kilgore Committee, 1944 (23a)
- Post War World Council, The Future of the Far East, 1944 (23a)
- Post War World Council, Self-Determination for Puerto Rico, 1946 (23a)
- University of Puerto Rico, Patterns of Living Puerto Rican Families, 1949 (23a)
- Labor Tends and Social Welfare in Latin America, 1939-1940, 1941 (23a)
- A Peace to End Tyranny, Poverty and War (23a)
- Pan American Union, Pan American Day Handbook, A Guide for Use in Organizing Specials Programs or Celebrations for Observance of "The Day of the Americans", 1952 April 14 (Box 24)
- Pan American Union, Guia de Servicio Social en America Latina, 1953 (Box 24)
- Pan American Union, Directerio de Instituciones de Vivienda y Planeamiento, 1953 (Box 24)
- Pan American Union, Organization of American States Directory, 1953 (Box 24)
- Pan American Union, Catalogue of Pan American Union Publications, 1951 (Box 24)
- Pan American Union, Catalogue of Pan American Union Publications, 1951 (Box 24)
- Pan American Union, Publications of the Pan American Union, in English, Spanish, Portuguese, and French, 1950 (Box 24)
- National Council of Social Service, The Thirty Sixth Annual Report of the National Council of Social Service, 1955 (Box 24)
- National Council of Social Service, The Thirty Seventh Annual Report of the National Council of Social Service, 1956 (Box 24)
- National Council of Social Service, Opportunity and Initiative, Annual Report, 1948-1949, 1950 (Box 24)
- National Council of Social Service, Voluntary Service: Annual Report of the National Council of Social Service, 1942-1943 (Box 24)
- National Information Bureau, Report of a Study of the Interrelation of the Work of National Social Agencies in Fourteen American Communities, 1923 (Box 24)
- National Information Bureau (N.Y.). Commission on Russian Relief, The Russian Families, 1921-1922, 1922-1923 (Box 24)
- National Information Bureau, Wise Giving Bulletin, 1950-1963 (Box 24)
- National Information Bureau Newsletters and Reports (Box 24)
- New York State Department of Health, Monthly Vital Statistics Review, Vol. 17-18, 1936-1937 (Box 24)
- State Bureau of Labor Statistics, Third Biennial Report of the Bureau of Labor Statistics of the State of California for Years 1887-1888 (Box 24)
- Children's Mission to the Children of the Destitute, The First Annual Report of the Executive Committee of the Children's Mission to the Children of the Destitute, 1850-1875 (Box 24)
- Irish Public Health Council, Report o the Irish Public Health Council on the Public Health and Medical Services in Ireland, 1920 (Box 24)
- A Selected Bibliography of Recent Publications on the Helpful Relations of Employers and Employed, 1912 (Box 24)
- Bureau of Statistics of Labor, The Annual Statistics of Manufacturers 1898, 1899 (Box 24)
- The Educational Finance Inquiry Commission, The Financing of Public Schools in the State of Illinois, 1924 (Box 24)
- National Consumer Finance Association, Consumer Installment Loans, a Bibliography Selected and Annotated, 1945 (Box 24A)
- A Guide to the Study of Occupations; A Selected Critical Bibliography of the Common Occupations with Specific References for the Study, 1921 (Box 24A)
- The American Medico-Psychological Association, The American Journal of Insanity, 1919-1920 (Box 24A)
- Church Missions House, A Social Service Program for the Parish (Box 24A)
- Church Missions House, Social Study Series, No. 1: What is Social Service? (Box 24A)
- Church Missions House, Social Study Series, No. 2: The Social Teaching of the Prophets (Box 24A)
- Church Missions House, Social Study Series, No. 6-7: Social Aspects of Church History, the Early Period (Box 24A)
- Church Missions House, A Suggested Canon of Provincial Boards of Social Service (Box 24A)
- Church Missions House, The Joint Commission on Social Service (Box 24A)
- Church Missions House, What the Joint Commission on Social Service has Accomplished (Box 24A)
- Church Missions House, The "One Per Cent" Apportionment for Social Service (Box 24A)
- Church Missions House, The Layman's Opportunity for Social Service (Box 24A)
- Church Missions House, Some Lending Community Churches (Box 24A)
- Church Missions House, Service, Semi-Annual Report of the Executive Secretary, Submitted 1915 May 6 (Box 24A)
- New York, Joint Commission on Social Service of the Protestant Episcopal Church, The Challenge of the City, 1918 (Box 24A)
  Scope and Contents
  Based on a Sermon Preached at St. John's Church, Elizabeth, NJ, 1918 February 3
- Church Missions House, Childhood Ventures in Christian Service, 1926 (Box 24A)
- New York, Joint Commission on Social Service of the Protestant Episcopal Church, Parish Questionnaire (Box 24A)
- New York, Joint Commission on Social Service of the Protestant Episcopal Church, How to Conduct a Parish Social Service Canvass (Box 24A)
- New York, Joint Commission on Social Service of the Protestant Episcopal Church, Social Service for Diocesan Commissions, 1912 (Box 24A)
- What is Christian Social Service (Box 24A)
- National Council of the Churches of Christ in the United States of America, National Council Outlook, 1951 January-1953 May, various issues (Box 25)
- Board of Commissioner of the Central Park, Eleventh Annual Report of the Board of Commissioners of the Central Park, for the Year Ending 1867 December 31, 1868 (Box 25)
- Educational Finance Inquiry Commission, The Cost of Education in California, a Statistical Study of the Costs for Elementary, Secondary, and Higher Education in the State, Based on the Returns for the School Year 1921-1922, 1924 (Box 25)
- Occupational Therapy for the Mentally and Nervously Ill, 1925 (Box 25)
- United States.; Bureau of the Census, Financial Statistics of Cities having a Population of Over 30,000, 1925 (Box 25)
- The Finns in America, a Bibliographical Guide to Their History, 1947 (Box 25)
- Bureau of Statistics of Labor, The Annual Statistics of Manufacturers 1897, 1898 (Box 25)
- Bureau of Statistics of Labor, The Annual Statistics of Manufacturers 1899, 1900 (Box 25)
- United States.; Bureau of Labor Statistics, Convention of Marine Cooks and Stewards of Pacific Coast, 1945 July 23-28 (Box 25)
- New York Department of Parks, Minutes and Documents of the Board of Commissioners of the Department of Parks of the Year Ending 1898 April 30 (Box 25)
- New York Department of Parks, Minutes and Documents of the Board of Commissioners of the Department of Parks of the Year Ending 1894 April 30 (Box 25)
- Housing Administration: A Practical Handbook for the Use of Public Health Officials an Others Interested in Housing, 1935 (Box 25)
- Bureau of Municipal Research (Philadelphia, PA), Auditing Control and Purchasing Procedure in the Municipal Court of Philadelphia, Reports by the Bureau of Municipal Research of Philadelphia of Two Studies Made by it as Agent of the Thomas Skelton Harrison Foundation, 1930 (Box 25)
- The Near East Foundation, The Near East Foundation Progress Report 1933 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, The Near East Foundation Progress Report 1934 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, The New Urgency (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Heads Hands Hearts, 1958 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Report of Lard W. Archer, Foreign Director, 1934-1935 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Report of Lard W. Archer, Foreign Director, 1934-1935, 1937 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Report of Lard W. Archer, Foreign Director, 1934-1935, 1938 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Report of Lard W. Archer, Foreign Director, 1934-1935, 1938 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Near East Foundation Annual Report 1938-1939 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of the Educational Director, 1947 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of the Foreign Director 1941-1942 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of the Foreign Director 1946-1947 (Box 26)
- A Model Housing Law, 1920 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Christmas Greetings, 1960 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Season's Greetings, 1958 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Summit at the Grassroots (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, 1971 Annual Report, 1972 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of the Near East Foundation in Iran from 1954 July 1 to 1955 June 30 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Foreign Director's Annual Report 1949-1950 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of Educational Director, 1950 October (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of Educational Director, 1951 October (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of Educational Director, 1952 October (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of Educational Director, 1953 October (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of Director of Programs, 1954 October (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of Educational Director, 1956 October (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of Educational Director, 1947 October (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of Foreign Director, 1947-1948 (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of Educational Director, 1948 October (Box 26)
- The Near East Foundation, Annual Report of Educational Director, 1949 December (Box 26)
- Committee on Child Development, Child Development Abstracts and Bibliography (Box 26)
- Greenwich House Annual Report 1950, 1951 (Box 26)
- Greenwich House Annual Report 1939, 1940 (Box 26)
- Greenwich House Thirty-Eight 1940 Annual Report (Box 26)
- Greenwich House 1943 1944 (Box 26)
- Greenwich House 1942 1943 (Box 26)
- Greenwich House 1944 1945 (Box 26)
- Greenwich House Annual Report 1947 (Box 26)
- Greenwich House Annual Report 1949 (Box 26)
- University of Puerto Rico Social Science Research Division, The Net Income of the Puerto Rican Economy 1940-1944 (Box 26)
- University of Puerto Rico Social Science Research Division, Annual Report Social Science Center, 1949-1959 (Box 26)
- Chicago Home for the Friendless, Forty-First Annual Report of the Chicago Home for the Friendless for the 1899 (Box 26)
- Near East Foundation Annual Report of the Director of Programs, 1955 December (Box 26)
- Die Arbeiter-Versorgung, 1909 (Box 27)
- National Information Bureau, Wise Giving Bulletin, 1950-1963 (Box 27)
- New York State Department of Social Welfare, Annual Medical Utilization Rates in the Old-Age Assistance Programs in 34 Selected Districts in Upstate New York, 1957 July-1958 June (Box 27)
- Menninger Foundation, Menninger Quarterly, 1955 Spring (Box 27)
- Tennessee Department of Public Welfare, Public Welfare in Tennessee, 1967 (Box 27)
- State Department of Pensions and Security, Alabama Social Welfare, 1976 October (Box 27)
- United States Bureau of the Census, Religious Bodies 1926, 1930 (Box 27)
- American Statistical Association, American Agricultural Villages: 1930, 1933 (Box 27)
- Russell Sage Foundation, Social Work Year Book (Box 27)
- Harvard University Press, Handbook of Latin American Studies, 1944, 1947 (Box 27)
- Bibliography on Consumer Education, 1939 (Box 27)
- U. S. Government, Fifteenth Census of the United States, 1930, 1933 (Box 27A)
- Preventing Crime, 1936 (Box 27A)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Social Work, 1930 (Box 27A)
- United States Bureau of the Census, Birth, Stillbirth, and Infant Mortality Statistics for the Continental United States, the Territory of Hawaii, the Virgin Islands, 1931-1936 (Box 27A)
- United States Bureau of the Census, Financial Statistics of Cities Having a Population of Over 100,000, 1936, 1937-1938 (Box 27A)
- United States Bureau of the Census, Religious Bodies: 1916, 1919 (Box 28)
- Washington Government Printing Office, Statistical Abstract of the United States, 1929 (Box 28)
- US Government, Thirteenth Census of the United States, 1914 (Box 28)
- US Government, Thirteenth Census of the United States, 1914 (Box 28)
- United States Bureau of the Census, Religious Bodies - 1916, 1919 (Box 29)
- United States Bureau of the Census, Wealth, Debt, and Taxation, 1915 (Box 29)
- United Stated Congress, House, Statistical Abstract of the United States 1913, 1919 (Box 29)
- United States Bureau of the Census, Wealth, Debt, and Taxation 1922: Estimated National Wealth, 1924 (Box 29)
- Woodrow Wilson Collection, Bohemian (Cech) Bibliography: A Finding List of Writings in English, 1918 (Box 29)
- Michigan State Court of Mediation and Arbitration, Biennial Report of the State Court of Mediation and Arbitration, 1907-1908 (Box 29)
- American Friends Service Committee, International Relief in Action, 1914-1943, 1944 (Box 29)
- United States Immigration Commission, The Children of Immigrants in Schools (Box 29)
- Report of the Board of Managers of the Pennsylvania Hospital, 1892 (Box 30)
- Bulletin of Iowa Institutions, Volumes III, 1901 (Box 30)
- United States Census Bulletins 1900 (Box 30)
- Thirteenth Census of the United States Taken in the Year 1909, Volume III, Manufacturers, 1913 (Box 30)
- United States Census Bulletins 1920-1927 (Box 30)
- Decimal Classification and Relative Index, 1932 (Box 31)
- The Co-operative Wholesale Societies, Ltd., Annual, 1895, 1906 (Box 31)
- Tuberculosis Commission of Maryland, Report of the Tuberculosis Commission of the State of Maryland, 1902-1904 (Box 31)
- International Labour Office, Industrial and Labour Information, 1940 April-June (Box 31)
- National Recreation Association, 25th National Recreation Congress Proceedings, 1940 September 30-October 4 (Box 31)
- Harvard University Press, Handbook of Latin American Studies, 1948 (Box 31)
- Permanent Court of International Justice, Affaire Concernant la Paiement de Divers Emprunts Serbes emais en France (Box 31)
- Bibliography of the Island of Guam, 1939 (Box 31)
- National Tuberculosis Association, A Directory of Sanatoria, Hospitals, Day Camps and Preventoria for the Treatment of Tuberculosis in the United States, 1923 (Box 31)
- New York State Industrial Commission, The Industrial Bulletin, 1924-1930 (Box 31)
- National Recreation Association, First International Recreation Congress Proceedings, 1932 July 23-29 (Box 32)
- Census Bulletin Statistics of Manufactures, 1890 (Box 32)
- Associated Charities of Boston, A Directory of Charitable and Beneficent Organizations of Boston, 1899 (Box 32)
- Associated Charities of Boston, A Directory of Charitable and Beneficent Organizations of Boston, 1907 (Box 32)
- Associated Charities of Boston, A Directory of Charitable and Beneficent Organizations of Boston, 1914 (Box 32)
- Preventing Crime: A Symposium, 1936 (Box 32)
- Technical Education. Its Development and Aims, 1925 (Box 32)
- Rand School of Social Science, Political Issues Facing American Labor, An Imperial Obligation - Industrial Villages for Partially Disabled Soldiers and Sailors, 1917 (Box 32)
- Harvard University Press, Handbook of Latin American Studies, 1946 (Box 32)
- Commodity Flow and Capital Formation, 1938 (Box 33)
- Great Britain Royal Commission on Labour, Reports by William E. Bear, Upon Ceretain Selected Districts in the Counties of Bedford, Hampshire, Huntingdon, Leicester, Nottingham, and Sussex, 1893 (Box 33)
- Bibliography of Industrial Hygiene, Volumes 2-15, 1926-1941 (Box 34)
- Biennial Census of Manufactures, 1921, 1924 (Box 34)
- Report of the Survey of the Schools of Newburgh, New York, 1929 (Box 34)
- The Report of a Survey of the Public Schools of Newark, New Jersey - Made by the Division of Field Studies, Institute of Educational Research, Teachers College, Columbia university. (Box 35)
- Report of the Survey of the Schools of Lynn, Massachusetts, 1927 (Box 35)
- Proceedings of the Third Conference of Teachers of International Law Held in Washington, D.C., 1928 April 25-26 (Box 35)
- Proceedings of the Fourth Conference of Teachers of International Law and Related Subjects, Held at Briarcliff Lodge, New York, 1929 October 10-17 (Box 35)
- Proceedings of the Fifth Conference of Teachers of International Law and Related Subjects, Held at Washington, D. C., 1933 April 26-27 (Box 35)
- Proceedings of the Sixth Conference of Teachers of International Law and Related Subjects, Held at Washington, D. C., 1938 April 27-30 (Box 35)
- Proceedings of the Seventh Conference of Teachers of International Law and Related Subjects, Held at Washington, D. C., 1941 April 23-25 (Box 35)